Guide to the Global Fund for Women Records SC0671
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Global Fund for Women records
1964-2014
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Global Fund for Women
SC0671
32 Linear Feet (22 boxes)
Files from Anne Firth Murray's tenure as Founding President of the Global Fund for Women (1987-1996).
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Anne Firth Murray, 2002; 2015; 2016.
Biographical/Historical note
The Global Fund for Women was founded in Palo Alto, Calif. in 1987 by Anne Firth Murray, Frances Kissling and Laura Lederer. Its mission is to support women's rights by providing grant funds to women's organizations throughout the world. Since its founding, it has raised nearly $85 million in donor funds and has provided grants to 4200 groups in 171 countries.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of files from Anne Firth Murray's tenure as Founding President of the Global Fund for Women (1987-1996). Included are chronological files from Firth and other administrators, correspondence, clippings and articles, press releases and other promotional materials, and meeting and event files.
Related Materials
See also the Global Fund for Women Collection at Mills College.
Women in development; Women's rights -- Developing countries; Global Fund for Women; Global Fund for Women; Murray, Anne Firth.; Global Fund for Women; Murray, Anne Firth.
- Records, Accession ARCH-2002-203
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 1/88-6/88 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 7/88-10/88 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 11/88-12/88 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 4/89 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 1/89-3/89 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 5/89 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 6/89 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 7/89 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 10/89 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 8/89-9/89 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 11/89 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 12/89 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 2/90 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 1/90 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 4/90 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 3/90 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- June 1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- 5/90 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- Aug. 1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- July 1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- Dec. 1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- November 1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- October 1990 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- September 1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- Jan. 1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- Feb. 1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- Mar. 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- Apr. 1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- June 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- May 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- July 1-24, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- July 25-Sept. 30, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- July 25-31, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- November 1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- October 1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- Dec. 13-31, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File -- Dec. 1-12, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Inquiries -- March 14, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Inquiries -- Feb. 89 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Inquiries -- Nov. 88-Feb. 89 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Inquiries -- June 88-Oct. 88 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Inquiries -- July 87-May 88 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Inquiries -- September 1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Inquiries -- Aug 18-Aug 31, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Inquiries -- August 15, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Inquiries -- July 26-August 11 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Inquiries -- July 15, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Inquiries -- July 26, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Inquiries -- July 6, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Inquiries -- May 5, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Inquiries -- April 18, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Inquiries -- April 11, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Inquiries -- April 4, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Inquiries -- March 10, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Inquiries -- March 1990 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Inquiries -- February 1990 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Inquiries -- January 1990 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Inquiries - December 1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Inquiries - November 1989 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Inquiries - October 1989 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Inquiries -- July 1990 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Inquiries -- June 1990 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Inquiries -- May 1990 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Inquiries -- April 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Inquiries -- November 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Inquiries -- October 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Inquiries -- September 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Inquiries -- August 1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Inquiries -- July 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Inquiries -- March 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Inquiries -- May 1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Inquiries -- April 1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Inquiries -- March 1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Inquiries -- June 1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Inquiries -- May 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Inquiries -- April 1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Inquiries -- February 1991 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Inquiries -- January 1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Inquiries -- December 1992 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Inquiries -- November 1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Inquiries -- October 1992 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Inquiries -- September 1992 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Inquiries -- July 1992 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Inquiries -- June 1992 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Inquiries -- January 1991 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Inquiries -- December 1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Inquiries -- November 1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Inquiries -- October 1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Inquiries -- September 1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Inquiries -- August 1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Liz Laughead Chron File -- 1988 Jan-June (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth J. Laughead Chron File -- 7/88-12/88 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Ann Wright Chron File -- Oct. Nov. Dec. 1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Ann Wright Chron File -- Jul. Aug. Sept. 1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Ann Wright Chron File -- Apr. May Jun. 1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Ann Wright Chron File -- Jan. Feb. Mar. 1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Wright Chron File -- 10/90-12/90 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Wright Chron File -- 4/90-6/90 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Wright Chron File -- 7/90-9/90 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- October-December 1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- May-September 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- July 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- 6/91 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- 4/1/91-5/31/91 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- 2/91-3/91 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Chron File Mila Visser 'T Hooft -- July-October 1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- Jan-Feb 1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- 9/90-11/90 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- 6/89-9/89 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- 8/91-10/91 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- 12/90-1/91 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- November 1993-April 1994 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- May and June 1993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- March and April 1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- 2/92-4/92 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- 11/91-1/92 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- 8/92-12/92 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Mila Visser 'T Hooft Chron File -- 5/92-7/92 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Jasmin Schwarz Chron Files for 6/92-7/92 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Jasmin Schwarz Chron Files for 4/92-5/92 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Jasmin Schwarz Chron Files for 1/92-3/92 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Jasmin Schwarz Chron Files for 11/91-12/91 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Jasmin Schwarz Chron Files for 10/91 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Jasmin Schwarz Chron Files for 9/91 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Jasmin Schwarz Chron Files for 1/91-8/91 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Jasmin Schwarz Chron Files for 10/90-12/90 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Marea Wexler Chron File -- 2/90-6/90 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Marea Wexler Chron (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Cara Page Chron File (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Gretchen Sutphen May 1992 Chron File -- May 1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- April 1992 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- March 1992 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 2/92 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- January 1992 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- December 1991 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- November 1991 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 10/91 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 9/91 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 8/91 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 7/91 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 6/91 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 5/91 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 4/91 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 3/91 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 2/91 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 1/91 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 7/91 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 12/90 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 11/90 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 10/90 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 9/90 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 8/90 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 7/90 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 6/90 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 5/90 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 4/90 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Gretchen Sutphen Chron File -- 1/90-3/90 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Tara Brown Chron File -- 1/89-3/89 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Tara L. Brown Chron File - 4/89-5/89 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Tara L. Brown Chron File - 6/89-7/89 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Tara L. Brown Chron File - 8/89-9/89 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Tara L. Brown Chron File - 10/89-12/89 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence / Tara's through December '88 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Judith Edelman Chron File - 9/89-12/89 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Judith Edelman Chron File -- 1/90-3/90 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Judith Edelman Chron File - 4/89-6/89 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Judith Edelman Chron File - 7/89-9/89 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Renu Karir Chron File -- 9/90-1/91 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Chron File Judith Kleinberg -- 4/88-6/88 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Judith G. Kleinberg Chron File -- 7/88-12/88 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Elizabeth J. Laughead Chron File -- 10/89-12/89 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Elizabeth J. Laughead Chron File -- 1/90-3/90 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Elizabeth J. Laughead Chron File -- 1/89-3/89 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Elizabeth J. Laughead Chron File -- 4/89-6/89 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Elizabeth J. Laughead Chron File -- 7/89-9/89 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Liz Laughead Chron File - 1987 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Dublin Popov Chron File -- 8/89-12/89 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Neera Kuckreja Sohoni Chron File -- 11-12/89 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Gretchen Sutphen July 1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Gretchen Sutphen June 1992 Chron File (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Gretchen Sutphen /Chron File August 1992 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Gretchen Sutphen /Chron File September 1992 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Gretchen Sutphen /Chron File October 1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Misc. Singapore Meeting Info. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Gretchen Sutphen /Chron File December 1992 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File April 1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File March 1992 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File February 1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File January 1992 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File July 1992 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File June 1992 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File May 1992 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File April 1993 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File March 1993 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File February 1993 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File January 1993 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File December 1992 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File November 1992 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File October 1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File September 1992 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File August 1992 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File July 1993 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File June1993 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File May 1993 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File October 1993 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File September 1993 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File August 1993 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File December 1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Anne Firth Murray Chron File November 1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Women Organizing, Empowering Themselves
    - Unfoldered clippings and articles (Box 8)
    - Activist mothers: Las Madres de Plaza de Mayo, Argentina (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Women and Money (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Economic Development
    - Grameen Bank, Bangladesh (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Women and economic development, general overview (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Structural Adjustment's effect on women (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Women and Agriculture (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Education/Training
    - Education/population control link (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Female education -- global indicators (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Public Service Announcements
    - KBAY PSA, 9/19/95 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Speakers' event PSA (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Ethel Santiago, KEZR 106.5fm (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Radio PSAs, generic (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - KBAY radio editorial, 11/15/93 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - TV PSA drafts (Mairi) (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - TV PSA workshop, 2/1/94 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Sierra Club PSAs (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Press Contacts
    - Press mailing list -- positive responses (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Press mailing list -- negative responses (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Press list: FHR issues from Communications Consort. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Speakers' Event
    - Possible speaking engagements (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Speakers (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Arrangements with Covenant Church, Palo Alto (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Fliers and invitations (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - PSAs / press contacts for event (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Conference Participation
    - Professional and Businesswomen's Conference, 5/12/94 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - ODN Global Objectives Conference, 4/94 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Berkeley Earth Day, 4/23/94 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - World Forum of Silicon Valley Spring 1994 speakers' event (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Presbytery of San Jose, 2/94 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Press Correspondence
    - Ellen Kranick/Gen. Fed. Of Women's Clubs 8/94 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Maryland TV Transcripts Latin America (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Personalized requests for GFW info, 1/94-6/94 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Roger MacDonald, Gorbachev Fdn. (Research Resources) (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Misti's article (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Nikki Anderson / Ms magazine Innternational Women's good news (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - SF Chronicle correspondence fall 1994 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Country Almanac 7/8/93 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Tim Carrington, Wall Street Journal, 3/94 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Sara Beckman, SJ Mercury News editorial, Spring 1994 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Global Vision Television / Daughters' Education, Thai. (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Women's Feature Service / Donors' Circle Article, 2/94 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - KPFA FM (Berkeley) Cathy Chapman, Women's Dept. (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Kai-Ping Liu, Sing Tao Daily South San Francisco (Chinese), 3/30/94 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Jessica Lloyd Rogers, KKUP Radio, Cupertino 3/94 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Barbara Burnett, Family Health International (NC) (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Media-related correspondence ICPD, Cairo, Sept. 1994 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Letters resulting from 6/93 Mercury News article (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Letter to ABC Television; Female genital mutilation, 9/93 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Letter to Christian S.M. organizing against violence, 8/93 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence with Daphne White re: UAL article, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence with Metro (local paper -- Jeff Brock), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Media solicitations for GFW information -- past, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence with Chicago Tribune
      - Ongoing correspondence with Jim Musser (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - Norma Libman, Taiwan 3/94 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - Follow-up correspondence, female genital mutilation, 9/23/93 (Box 8, Folder 57)
      - Initial correspondence -- grantee summaries (Box 8, Folder 58)
      - Material passed on to Sharon Miller 9/93 (Box 8, Folder 59)
      - Unfoldered newspapers and clippings (Box 8)
      - Calendar / post-Beijing publicity events (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Grantees in the press (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Chicago Tribune, Profile of Chi-Ching Shih, Awakening Fdn, etc. (Box 8, Folder 62)
      - Pieces for Non-Profit Directories/Compendiums (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - Daphne White -- journalist and philanthropist (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - Media Alliance 7/14/92 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - Media Alliance workshops (Box 8, Folder 66)
      - Media Alliance information (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - Current media events (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - Important media strategies (Box 8, Folder 69)
      - Press contacts (Box 8, Folder 70)
      - Marketing Ideas (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Press kit updates, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Press correspondence 1/96-6/96 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Background to March 1996 CRM campaign, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Women's Rights and the Global Economy, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - La Gazette, Santa Cruz, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Stacey's [Bookstore] press release, 3/96 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Georgetown Journal on Poverty, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Feb. Grants release, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Scrivener Award, April 1996 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Press inquiries, Spring 1996 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Jean Tepperman, Bay Guardian, SF Chron. Articles, spring 94 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Susie Siegal, Tampa Tribune 8/95 (interviewed Laurie) (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Marilynn Lewis, SJ Mercury, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Women and Water article for Waterworks magazine 5/94 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Press kit estimates, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - International Women's Day PSAs, 3/8/95 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Status of Girls Worldwide, Lillian/Mairi's article, NOW, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Maria Guara, SF Chronicle, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Press correspondence, 7/95-12/95 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Press correspondence, 1/96-6/96 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Impact Visuals -- photographers, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Press Packet -- Specific Materials
    - The Global Fund for Women in support of female human rights worldwide (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Women in the World (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Press Releases
    - Sample Press Kit, Spring 1996 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - March 1996 campaign -- Stacey's Joins Campaign press release (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - March 1996 campaign -- Bay Area-Specific press release (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Press Release -- May Lin Oct. 1995 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Press Release -- October grants 1995 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Press Release -- Beijing grants 1995 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Sisters and Daughters Betrayed press release 1995 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Press Release -- Beijing workshops 1995 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - March 1995 press release (grants) (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - October 1994 press release (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - June grants release, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Press / Valya Konstantinova's visit, 6/20/94-7/1/94 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Anne / Soroptimists press release -- June 1994 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - February 1994 press release (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Donors' Circle press release Jan. 1994 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Tabra press release Dec. 1993 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Luchie press release Nov. 1993 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - October 1993 Press Releases (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - June 1993 Grants/Malta Press Release (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Opportunities for Publication: Ms Magazine (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Opportunities for Publication: Writers/journals to target for publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Opportunities for Publication: target journals for publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Women/politics brief sheets background (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Women's Reading/ O. Lipovskaia (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Women East-West Newsletter (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Montage The Soviet-American Student Journal (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Dialogue on Diversity (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Enterprise Development Program (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Paul Strasburg -- Volunteers in Asia - Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Somerville, Bill Philanthropic Ventures Foundation (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Genie Laborde (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Norman Fleishman (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Sarah Harder (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Tom Fox (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Collette Shulman (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Quadrus 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Contacts: Russian (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Dubna Report (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Dubna Conference, March 1991 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Soviet Women Organizations (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Dubna Conference 1992 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - How to Apply for a Grant (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Center for Gender Studies (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - US Women / Organizations (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - USSR General Information (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - FSU: Resources (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Russia: To Do (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Temporary Assistance (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Marguerite Gee (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Bill Carpenter (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Cecilia Cyrier (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Board Book October 1993 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Board Advance 10/9/92 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Board Retreat -- July '92 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Johnnetta B. Cole (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Board of Directors Correspondence FY 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Board of Directors Correspondence FY 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Board of Directors Correspondence FY 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Board Memos Fys 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Jamie L Langlie (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Maureen K. Porter (Box 9, Folder 47)